

Flushing, NY • tiffany lo[at]icloud.com

WWW tiffanylo.dev • LINKEDIN /tiffanylocodes • GITHUB /missamii

"Before attending General Assembly. At twelve years old I was already dabbling heavily in design + code. Today, my mission is to create a beautiful web and to use sustainable tech to accomplish this. I am the people's Developer who advocates for user experience."

SKILLS

HTML5/CSS3 • PHP • Ruby • JavaScript • ¡Query • ES6 • Ruby on Rails • PostgreSQL MongoDB • SQL • MySQL • React.JS • Express • Node.JS • API • Paint Shop Pro X •

Web Hosting • FTP • Greensock

EXPERIENCE

05.2018 - current CHAYN Global • Executive Director & Tech Lead

02.2018 - 05.2018 Content Writer & Social Media

12.2017 - 06.2018 2 Market Media Remote • Freelance Front End Developer

Creates and maintains landing pages and websites. Using a range of technologies such as-

PHP, HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

08.2017 - 08.2017 CiFiCo Melville, NY • JavaScript Animator

Animated SVGs and created SVGs. Using pure vanilla JavaScript and a third-party animation

library, Greensock. Front End: CSS, HTML5, Javascript, Greensock library.

03.2017 - 08.2017 Global Telecom Supply Roslyn, NY • Full Stack Web Developer

Created and maintain their website and backend. I brought to them their first and official in house code base. Front End: JavaScript & jQuery, Bootstrap, HTML/CSS. Back End: PHP,

MySQL/SQL, JavaScript.

11.2016 - current Tiffany Lo Designs Remote • Full Stack Web Developer Freelancer

I present my client's with attractive, functional websites and applications to make their products and services stand out to a wide audience. Using a range of technologies to make their goals a reality. Past Client(s): Kyle Moore - Theme for Website; Frontend: HTML, CSS, W3.CSS framework. Backend: PHP, MySQL & Landing Page; Frontend: ¡Query, Bulma

framework.

VOLUNTEER

02.2017 - 03.2017 ScriptEd Inc. The Young Women's Leadership School, New York, NY • Academic Web Developer

Gave high school students a push and introduction into STEM. Laving down the fundamentals of HTML, CSS and JavaScript. So they can be equipped to build their own websites and

games.

EDUCATION

General Assembly New York, NY • Full Stack Web Development The Art Institute of New York City New York, NY • Graphic Design